{
    "id": "06a4ff0c943f47fba4e639e97e23ab82",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Do you know …………………………. has happened?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He always preaches …………………………………….. he never practices.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the book …………………………………… I lent you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He has no sword with ………………………………. to fight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the man ………………………………….. purse was lost?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I met a man …………………………………… had just returned from America.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Only he …………………………………. wears the shoe knows where it pinches.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "who",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ………………………………. my grandfather built.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The spectators applauded the batsman ……………………………………. performance was spectacular.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………………. the gods love die young.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Which",
                "Whom"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}